Dendy Dharmawan

Web Developer

hiroto.monopoly@gmail.com

+62895615461125

dendy-dharmawan.vercel.app

I have worked as a Full Stack Web Developer for more than 7+ years and have worked on more than 20 website projects and 10 Android WebView application projects. Sometimes I also open side freelance services to work on website projects and Android WebView applications. I developed with a strong focus on innovation and user-centric design. Brings extensive experience in crafting responsive, mobile-friendly websites that deliver exceptional user experiences.

Experience

Freelance Web Developer

2017 - 2020

- Worked on more than 20 website projects and 10 Android WebView application projects.
- Developed various kinds of web pages such as Web landing pages, School Websites, Student Assignment Websites, Marketplace Websites and Company Websites.
- Designed website pages according to client requests.
- · Worked on projects according to estimated work time.
- · Create a CMS to manage client-side websites.

PT Krakatau Pipe Industries Web Programmer & IT Staff

2020 -2022

- Create or redesigned the main Company Profile Website using WordPress.
- Created an E-Invoice Website for Vendors for Company Business needs.
- Created a Company Internal Information System Management Website.
- Created a Dashboard / Interface Graphic Website from Complete Company Product Data.
- Create WhatsApp Bot for: Notifications, SAP Server Maintenance, Generate PDF CV & Remuneration Slip, etc.

Telkom Indonesia Web Developer

2022 -2024

- Developed a product website with a focus on providing user-friendly interface pages using Nuxt.js to solve existing problems.
- Developed and maintained robust web applications, reducing system downtimes by 15%.
- Collaborated with UX/UI designers to create user-friendly interfaces, improving overall customer satisfaction.

Education

Politeknik Negeri Jakarta

2013 - 2017

- Bachelor's degree, Informatics Engineering
- GPA: 3.83

Skills

- PHP
- CodeIgniter 3
- JavaScript
- React JS

- JQuery
- AJAX
- Next JS
- Go lang

- Hubspot
- SEO
- MySQL